hello everyone i wanted to make one
extra video this week
because i
just had the idea to share a little bit
about the people that mean so much to me
and
consequently a little bit of my life
outside of these videos
and i
find
my husband
and my mother and my grandmother to be
people that really inspire me and always
help me feel better when i'm not at my
best and so i wanted to just add this
little video in as
just something extra
feel free to skip this
for next week for my more usual content
but yeah it was just an idea i had and
and i thought it would be really lovely
to
kind of chat with some people that i
love and share a little bit about them
with you
so i hope you enjoy i'm sending you my
love
i will see you soon
[Music]
[Laughter]
my name
yes
um so could you share where you grew up
i grew up in
puerto rico
in santorse
is
part of the capital san juan
and i lived in
i was born in barrio
and then we moved to
la samapoles which was a project
still in rio piedras area
is
[Music]
a
so you
were a first generation college student
right you moved um to the us right um
to new york right when what age were you
i was 22
22. and what was your experience like
there
it was very challenging i didn't know
english when i arrived it was very hard
for me to learn english because i was
living in a hispanic
community so i joined the
navy reserve
because i i thought going away and
and being
immersed in english
speaking
culture and people and and environment
will help me
even though there were a lot of
traumatic experiences it also made me
grow and i learned so much
be more self-reliant
coffee
um
[Music]
well it's just water
well
i want some fake tea
you want a sip of my fake teeth
[Music]
fake tea
mmm
i just if it's water in a mug i call it
tea
okay just makes sense to me
nobody
hello everyone at long last i have been
able to
uh have luke sit down
to dispel
a common statement are you my cameraman
i am not okay or cameraman do i have a
camera crew that films my videos you do
not okay
anyway trying to dispel some myths now
that i have a witness
how did we meet
would you say oh i just spilled tea on
myself however you want to say you were
really into it
you kind of ignored me for the first
couple minutes when we met
i don't think i even made icons no
yeah
we were kind of set up
on
kind of a blind group date honestly yeah
and um i uh
specifically you know i i was absolutely
not interested in a relationship at the
time i thought i wasn't
you just moved over here yeah yeah i
didn't know it was a group date until i
kind of got there pretty much and so i
was i was very upset
and so
luke
um unfairly received the brunt of
shoulder yeah
yeah but uh yeah you kept in contact i
think it took like two months
wasn't that before we went on a date or
a month or so yeah yeah close to a month
yeah yeah so
before you
accepted my invitation yeah
kept thrilling a little while yeah
we yeah we went to a lake for our first
date called cutthroat lake
and i mentioned it to my sister and she
felt like that was a very um concerning
name for a lake to go on your first date
but it all worked out nothing horrible
happened nope
you tried to get me to jump into the
water i did and i refused
there's still snow around the lake too
yeah glacial temperature water is
not my fault i couldn't get her to go
for it three years later i still haven't
been able to no
i noticed the other day um i was trying
to find a specific link
for my book and i put in the cottage
fairy on google and one of the first
questions that came up of recently
searched questions or i think
often popular searches is um is the
cottage very real
oh she's real and she's real all right
am i real
i know her
yeah
how does it feel um living with someone
else after spending so much time living
on your own because i think we both came
yeah very good question yeah it feels
wonderful
it's a very nice change of pace
one that i've been looking forward to
for a very long time
yeah yeah i feel the same way yeah
all right
well anyway here he is
thank you all if you made it this far
leave your questions down below and i'll
have him answer for you
that's the college baby
you just gotta reply me you got a few
hearts your flowers okay
rainbows at the end of each sentence
thank you everyone
[Music]
do
you